Inventory of the Medicine Bow National Forest (Wyo.) records, 1897-1987
University of Wyoming. American Heritage Center.
- Series V. Photographs, 1907-1985
  - Sub-series 1. Photographs Organized by Number, 1907-1968
    - Recreation Management - Scenic Attractions - Water Falls (2352.16), 1922-1926 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Recreation Management - Scenic Attractions - Wild Flowers (2352.17), undated (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Timber Management (2400), undated (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Timber Management - Administrative Studies - Forest Types - Pinon-Juniper (2402.1), 1940 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Timber Management - Administrative Studies - Forest Types - Aspen (2402.2), undated (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Timber Management - Administrative Studies - Forest Types - Douglas-Fir (2402.3), circa 1922 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Timber Management - Administrative Studies - Forest Types - Lodgepole Pine (2402.4), circa 1923 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Timber Management - Administrative Studies - Forest Types - Spruce Fir (2402.5), 1941 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Timber Management - Administrative Studies - Forest Types - Ponderosa Pine (2402.6), undated (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Timber Management - Administrative Studies - Forest Types - Miscellaneous (2402.9), 1926-1961 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Timber Management - Commercial Timber Sales - Cruising (2431.1), 1938 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Timber Management - Commercial Timber Sales - Presale Preparation - Growth Studies (2431.2), 1935 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Timber Management - Commercial Timber Sales - Presale Preparation - Marking (2431.4), circa 1912 (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Timber Management - Sales - Logging (2432.1), 1921-1949 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Timber Management - Sales - Logging (2432.1), 1914-1944 (Box 17, Folder 1-2)
    - Timber Management - Sales - Logging - Brush Disposal (2432.1a), undated (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Timber Management - Sales - Logging - Felling and Bucking (2432.1b), undated (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Timber Management - Sales - Logging - Camps and Mills (2432.1c), 1922-1928 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Timber Management - Sales - Logging - Skidding (2432.1d), 1935 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Timber Management - Sales - Logging - Loading (2432.1f), 1921-1944 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Timber Management - Sales - Logging - Hauling (2432.1g), 1923-1944 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Timber Management - Sales - Logging - Erosion Control (2432.1h), 1931-1956 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Timber Management - Sales - Logging - Roads (2432.1i), 1961 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Timber Management - Sales - Sawmills (2432.2), 1938-1949 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Timber Management - Sales - Sawmills - Machinery (2432.2a), 1914-1949 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Timber Management - Sales - Sawmills - Ponds (2432.2b), 1943 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Timber Management - Sales - Sawmills - Yards (2432.2d), 1914-1949 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Timber Management - Sales - Sawmills - Burners (2432.2e), circa 1917 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Timber Management - Sales - Sawmills - Planner Mill (2432.2f), undated (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Timber Management - Sales - Sawmills - Log Preservation (2432.2g), 1933-1938 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Timber Management - Sales - Silverculture Methods - Clearcut by Area (2432.3a), 1943-1949 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - Timber Management - Sales - Silverculture Methods - Cut by Strips (2432.3b), 1938-1953 (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - Timber Management - Sales - Waste - Defect (2432.4a), undated (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - Timber Management - Sales - Waste - Young Growth, Injury (2432.4d), undated (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - Timber Management - Sale Cruises, Marking, and Volume - Cruising (2441.1), 1938-1949 (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - Timber Management - Scaling and Measuring (2442), circa 1925 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Timber Management - Diseased Material (2461), undated (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Timber Management - Free Use (2463), circa 1925 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Timber Management - Reforestation - Camps (2470.1), undated (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Timber Management - Reforestation - Crews (2470.2), 1928-1936 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Timber Management - Reforestation - Equipment, Tools, Etc. (2470.3), circa 1936 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Timber Management - Reforestation - Operations (2470.4), 1912-1938 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Timber Management - Reforestation - Plantations (2470.5), 1929-1938 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Timber Management - Reforestation - Planting Sites (2470.6), 1928-1936 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Timber Management - Reforestation - Planting Stock (2470.7), undated (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Timber Management - Reforestation - Natural Reproduction (2470.9), 1921-1938 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Timber Management - Reforestation - Thinning (2470.11), 1933-1944 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Timber Management - Protection of Sales Areas - Hazard Reduction - Lopping and Scattering (2481.1), 1923-1924 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Timber Management - Protection of Sales Areas - Hazard Reduction - Piling and Burning (2481.2), 1907-1949 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Timber Management - Protection of Sales Areas - Hazard Reduction - Roadside Cleanup (2481.4), circa 1955 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Timber Management - Protection of Sales Areas - Insect and Disease Control (2483), 1935-1966 (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Timber Management - Protection of Sales Areas - Insect and Disease Control - Methods of Control (2483.3), 1934-1935 (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Watershed Management - Watershed Surveys and Plans (2510), 1949-1965 (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Watershed Management - Watershed Surveys and Plans - Water Resources (2511), 1965-1968 (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - Watershed Management - Watershed Surveys and Plans - Water Resources - Ditches and Flumes (2511.2), undated (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Watershed Management - Watershed Surveys and Plans - Water Resources - Reservoirs for Domestic Use (2511.5), 1964 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Watershed Management - Watershed Surveys and Plans - Floods - Watershed on which Flood Occurred (2512.1), circa 1926 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Watershed Management - Watershed Surveys and Plans - Floods - Flood Waters (2512.2), undated (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Watershed Management - Watershed Surveys and Plans - Floods - Damage (Property) (2512.3), 1953 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Watershed Management - Watershed Surveys and Plans - Floods - Erosion (2512.6), 1949 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Watershed Management - Watershed Surveys and Plans - Water Use - Domestic (2513.1), 1967 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Watershed Management - Water Resource Protection - Erosion Caused by Natural Causes (2520.7), circa 1931 (Box 19, Folder 8-9)
    - Watershed Management - Water Yield Improvement - Snow Surveys (2540.2), undated (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Wildlife Management - Wildlife Habitat (2630), 1968 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Wildlife Management - Wildlife Habitat - Improvement Projects (2630.1), 1922-1935 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Wildlife Management - Wildlife Habitat - Habitat Types (2630.2), 1923-1966 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Wildlife Management - Wildlife Habitat - Damage (2630.4), 1925 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Wildlife Management - Hunting, Fishing, Trapping - Big Game Species - Elk (2641.1), 1926 (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Wildlife Management - Hunting, Fishing, Trapping - Big Game Species - Deer (2641.2), 1933-1949 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Wildlife Management - Hunting, Fishing, Trapping - Big Game Species - Mountain Sheep (2641.3), 1928-1965 (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Wildlife Management - Hunting, Fishing, Trapping - Big Game Species - Bear (2641.4), 1938 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Wildlife Management - Hunting, Fishing, Trapping - Big Game Species - Antelope (2641.5), 1939 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Wildlife Management - Hunting, Fishing, Trapping - Small Game Species - Rabbits (2642.1), 1922-1926 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Wildlife Management - Hunting, Fishing, Trapping - Birds (2643), circa 1922 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Wildlife Management - Hunting, Fishing, Trapping - Birds - Grouse (2643.1), 1922-1933 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Wildlife Management - Hunting, Fishing, Trapping - Birds - Turkey (2643.2), circa 1944 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Wildlife Management - Hunting, Fishing, Trapping - Birds - Ptarmigan (2643.3), 1922-1943 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Wildlife Management - Hunting, Fishing, Trapping - Birds - Miscellaneous (2643.4), 1921-1925 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Wildlife Management - Hunting, Fishing, Trapping - Birds - Hawk (2643.5), 1925 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Wildlife Management - Hunting, Fishing, Trapping - Birds - Camp Robber (2643.6), circa 1926 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Wildlife Management - Hunting, Fishing, Trapping - Predatory Animals - Coyote (2644.1), 1926 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Wildlife Management - Hunting, Fishing, Trapping - Predatory Animals - Bob Cat (2644.4), undated (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Wildlife Management - Hunting, Fishing, Trapping - Predatory Animals - Miscellaneous (2644.5), circa 1966 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Wildlife Management - Hunting, Fishing, Trapping - Rodents - Porcupine (2645.3), undated (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Wildlife Management - Hunting, Fishing, Trapping - Rodents - Gophers (2645.5), undated (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Wildlife Management - Hunting, Fishing, Trapping - Rodents - Beavers (2645.6), 1928-1939 (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - Wildlife Management - Hunting, Fishing, Trapping - Rodents - Chipmunks (2645.7), undated (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - Wildlife Management - Hunting, Fishing, Trapping - Fishing (2647), 1939 (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - Wildlife Management - Hunting, Fishing, Trapping - Fishing - Catches (2647.4), 1922 (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - Wildlife Management - Hunting, Fishing, Trapping - Fishing - Planting (2647.7), undated (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - Land Use Management - Agriculture and Cultivation (2710.1), circa 1924 (Box 20, Folder 21)
    - Land Use Management - Camps (2710.3), 1926-1936 (Box 20, Folder 22)
    - Land Use Management - Residences (2710.9), 1915-1922 (Box 20, Folder 23)
    - Land Use Management - Resorts (2710.10), 1920-1938 (Box 20, Folder 24)
    - Land Use Management - Miscellaneous (2710.16), circa 1921 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Minerals Management - Lode Claims (2810.1), undated (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Minerals Management - Placer Claims (2810.2), undated (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Minerals Management - Quarries (2810.4), undated (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Minerals Management - Mining Camps (2810.7), undated (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Fire Control - Presuppression - Detection (5120.1), 1944-1945 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Fire Control - Presuppression - Equipment - Hand Tools (5120.2b), 1925-1938 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Fire Control - Presuppression - Equipment - Transportation (5120.2c), 1922-1925 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Fire Control - Presuppression - Equipment - Communication (5120.2d), 1942-1945 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Fire Control - Presuppression - Improvements (5120.7), 1912-1953 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Fire Control - Suppression - Fires Burning (5130.1), 1916-1955 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Fire Control - Suppression - Crews Working (5130.2), 1915-1966 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Fire Control - Suppression - Equipment Working (5130.3), undated (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Fire Control - Suppression - Fire Lines (5130.4), 1912-1966 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Fire Control - Suppression - Camps (5130.5), circa 1955 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Fire Control - Damage - Areas Burned (5140.1), 1915-1958 (Box 22, Folder 1-3)
    - Fire Control - Equipment and Supply Program - Safety (5160.4), 1928-1945 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Fire Control - Exchange (5430), 1942 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Fire Control - Claims and Reconveyances (5450), 1917-1937 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Fire Control - Helicopter Operations (5750), 1925-1961 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Personnel Management - Employment - Forest Officers (6110.1), 1903-1949 (Box 22, Folder 8-9)
    - Personnel Management - Employment - Forest Officers (6110.1), 1903-1965 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Engineering - Specialized Equipment - Miscellaneous Equipment (7120.3), 1922-1946 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Engineering - Land Line Location (7150), undated (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Engineering - Signs and Posters (7160), 1938-1961 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Engineering - Signs and Posters - Entrance Portals and Identification Markers (7160.3), 1936-1949 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Engineering - Signs and Posters - Information (7160.4), 1934-1960 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Engineering - Signs and Posters - Special, Site Entrance, Etc. (7160.5), undated (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Telephone Systems (7200.4), 1933-1938 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Buildings - Dwellings (7300.1), 1936-1945 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Buildings - Combination Buildings (7300.2), 1917-1955 (Box 23, Folder 10-12)
    - Buildings - Barns (7300.3), 1916-1942 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Buildings - Bunkhouses (7300.4), undated (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Buildings - Garages (7300.6), 1933-1940 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Buildings - Miscellaneous Buildings (7300.7), circa 1933 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Transportation Systems - Roads (7700.1), 1919-1966 (Box 24, Folder 5-8)
    - Transportation Systems - Roads (7700.1), 1919-1966 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Transportation Systems - Trails (7700.2), 1925-1939 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Transportation Systems - Bridges, Roads (7700.4), 1932-1933 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Transportation Systems - Bridges, Trails (7700.5), 1933-1936 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Transportation Systems - Culverts (7700.7), 1939 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Transportation Systems - Cattle Guards (7700.9), circa 1940 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Transportation Systems - Other (7700.12), 1915-1938 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Recreation (unnumbered), circa 1933 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - F.O. Field Trips (unnumbered), 1925-1941 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - F.O. Meetings (unnumbered), 1923-1931 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Miscellaneous and Unidentified (unnumbered), 1925-1937 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Sub-series 2. Photographs Organized Alphabetically, 1925-1956
    Contains photographs and negatives of plants, animals, operations, and the MBNF landscape. Images are similar and may even be duplicates of photographs found in sub-series 1, but they were organized according to one subject and arranged alphabetically.
    - After Fire, undated (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Agricultural and Mineral, undated (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Administrative, Range, and Recreation, 1938-1956 (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - Aspen, undated (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - Beaver, circa 1939 (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - Birds, undated (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - Boundary Post, 1939 (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - Bridges, undated (Box 26, Folder 20)
    - Buildings, undated (Box 26, Folder 21)
    - Buildings (other than), 1927 (Box 26, Folder 22)
    - Burned Over Areas, undated (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - Camping, 1939 (Box 25, Folder 19)
    - Camps, 1938 (Box 25, Folder 20)
    - Cattle, undated (Box 25, Folder 21)
    - Control Work, 1938 (Box 25, Folder 22)
    - Cutover Lands, undated (Box 25, Folder 23)
    - Departmental, 1926-1939 (Box 25, Folder 24)
    - Diseases, undated (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Equipment, Machinery, Tools, undated (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Earth, undated (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Erosion, Water, and Grazing, 1931 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Excursions, 1948 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Felling, 1927-1937 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Fir (by species), undated (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Fishing, circa 1939 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Floods, circa 1953 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Forest Officers, 1931-1933 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Fungus, undated (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Growth Studies, undated (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Individuals, 1925-1952 (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - Insects, 1934-1935 (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - Insect Control Work, undated (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - Lakes, undated (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - Loading, circa 1931 (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - Lookouts, 1929-1953 (Box 26, Folder 19)
    - Logging, undated (Box 26, Folder 23)
    - Marking, circa 1927 (Box 26, Folder 24)
    - Meetings (Ranger Training, etc.), 1925-1956 (Box 26, Folder 25)
    - Miscellaneous, 1938-1952 (Box 26, Folder 26)
    - Mountains, circa 1928 (Box 26, Folder 27)
    - National Forest, undated (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Nursery, 1938 (Box 26, Folder 28)
    - Peaks and Lookout Stations, 1927-1942 (Box 26, Folder 29)
    - Photographic Record, 1950 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Pine (by species), circa 1927 (Box 26, Folder 30)
    - Plantations, circa 1927 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Poisonous (Larkspurs, etc.), 1921 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Predatory Animals (by species), undated (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Range, 1949 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Range Sheep, 1927-1929 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Ranger Stations, 1938 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Rapids, undated (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Resorts (Other than special uses), 1920-1938 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Riding, undated (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Roads and Trails, 1924-1941 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Rock Formations, 1926-1940 (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Sanitation, Fountains, Toilets, circa 1956 (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Sawmills, 1937-1949 (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Scenic Attractions, 1938-1942 (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - Selection, Including Thinning and Pruning, 1927-1949 (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - Sheep, 1938 (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - Signs, undated (Box 27, Folder 18)
    - Silverculture Systems, undated (Box 27, Folder 19)
    - Skidding, Skids, Landings, 1935 (Box 27, Folder 20)
    - Skiing, 1941 (Box 27, Folder 21)
    - Spruce (By Species), 1937 (Box 27, Folder 22)
    - Stream Improvement, 1937 (Box 27, Folder 23)
    - Streams, circa 1927 (Box 27, Folder 24)
    - Ties, circa 1935 (Box 27, Folder 25)
    - Timberline, undated (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Timbersale Areas, 1927-1950 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Tools and Tool Boxes, undated (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Treating Plants, Etc., undated (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Watersheds and Drainages, undated (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Water Development, 1938 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Winter Scenes, undated (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Sub-series 3. Photographs, General, 1922-1985
    Contains a photo album and miscellaneous photographs.
    - Forest Work and Practices in the U.S. (Photo Album), undated (Box 28)
    - Miscellaneous Photographs, 1972-1976 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous Photographs, 1922-1985 (Box 33, Folder 18)
    - Pole Mountain, 1956 (Box 40, Folder 6)